musicsonglyrics.com 2014-02-22

# Privacy Policy | MusicSongLyrics.Com

**What data do we collect?**

We may collect data from you when you register on MusicSongLyrics, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

When browsing or registering on MusicSongLyrics, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MusicSongLyrics. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to yMusicSongLyricss and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [Opt Out page](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html). 

**What do we use your data for?**

Any of the data we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience   
(your data assists us to better respond to your individual needs) 

To improve MusicSongLyrics   
(we continually strive to improve MusicSongLyrics offerings based on the data and feedback we receive from you) 

To improve customer service   
(your data assists us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide may be used to send you data, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How do we protect your data?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal data when you enter, submit, or access your personal data. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you let) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain data 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with 3rd party service providers to assist us in better understanding MusicSongLyrics visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the data collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

**Do we disclose any data to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable data. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating MusicSongLyrics, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this data confidential. We may also release your data when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce MusicSongLyrics policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on MusicSongLyrics. These links and offers include [Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/), [eBay](http://www.amazon.com/) and other vendors. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of MusicSongLyrics and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any data from anyone under 13 years of age. MusicSongLyrics, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Third Party Ad Networks**

We let 3rd party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous data when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable data (e.g., click stream data, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this data. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to data collected through MusicSongLyrics and not to data collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using MusicSongLyrics, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
